[{"id": "5ff1423ab0ee8c595b6d39ab", "question": "What is the name of the thousand-year-old secret society depicted in \"The Da Vinci Code\"?", "answer": "Priory Of Sion", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c644", "question": "If a triangle has two equal sides, it is what?", "answer": "Isosceles", "category": "science"}, {"id": "59068076ff9c0647b50a808c", "question": "At what age did Prince release his debut album \"For You\"?", "answer": "19", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58dba6be874c93a3298b215b", "question": "What is the name of the long pole with a microphone attached at the end on a movie set?", "answer": "A boom", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fefbee06ce05a3942286ef8", "question": "Who recorded the song \"King for a Day\"?", "answer": "Thompson Twins", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5909cd9fbb53d1af658864ea", "question": "What is Santa\u2019s postal code in Canada?", "answer": "H0H 0H0", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b6b5", "question": "What fruit is normally squeezed into a margarita?", "answer": "Lime", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ffcfbd49dc5ec6cd98a8318", "question": "Who painted \"The Starry Night\"?", "answer": "Vincent van Gogh", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "60173e3544491cbd7c5a17ae", "question": "According to U.S. history, which is the \"date which will live in infamy\"?", "answer": "Dec. 7, 1941 -- The date the U.S. naval base, Pearl Harbor, was the target of a devastating surprise attack by Japanese forces.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339cfa", "question": "In which movie did Christina Ricci portray a witch?", "answer": "Sleepy Hollow", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "601b4b6649076251badbeac4", "question": "Maya Angelou spoke at the inauguration of which U.S. President?", "answer": "Maya Angelou recited her poem \"On the Pulse of Morning,\" at President Bill Clinton's first inauguration in 1993.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ff0b4a6e662d71a53650fed", "question": "Which Dutch artist painted \"Girl with a Pearl Earring\"?", "answer": "Vermeer", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fefc5086ce05a3942286f3a", "question": "What kind of gun does Harry Callahan use to kill Mick in the film \"Sudden Impact\"?", "answer": ".44 AMP Auto Mag Model 180", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fea7df4ff048f679a45ac03", "question": "Arachnophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Spiders", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339940", "question": "In the Foreigner song \"Hot Blooded\", the singer has a fever of what temperature?", "answer": "103", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f81", "question": "What was Billy J. Kramer's backing band?", "answer": "The Dakotas", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b7c", "question": "What did the letters in the name of the cable network HBO originally stand for?", "answer": "Home Box Office", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5af25699b63e5727cf5a483e", "question": "What is the general name of the game, \"Pogs\" that gained worldwide popularity in the mid 1990s?", "answer": "Milk caps", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ab99b0d21a8909e5c332d27", "question": "In which film did Marlene Dietrich sing \"See What the Boys in the Back Room Will Have\"?", "answer": "Destry Rides Again", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5937ee3208d98002fdd633d2", "question": "What is the literal meaning of the Dutch word \"brandewijn\"?", "answer": "Burned wine", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a820", "question": "What river forms much of the border between Washington and Oregon?", "answer": "Columbia River", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ae85e564007905755f79e87", "question": "If reading in chronological order, which book in \"The Chronicles of Narnia\" series should you read first?", "answer": "The Magician\u2019s Nephew", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c343", "question": "What is the sound a camel makes called?", "answer": "Nuzzing", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339796", "question": "Fond of flesh and fava beans, what bad guy was named the American film institutes top villain of all time?", "answer": "Hannibal Lecter", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe7c67c877e98cb977789ba", "question": "Where are the Mayan ruins of Tikal located?", "answer": "Guatemala", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59e80575de59ea584496feaa", "question": "Which actress played Emma Peel in the 1960s TV show \"The Avengers\"?", "answer": "Diana Rigg", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c2eb", "question": "What is the largest animal to have ever existed?", "answer": "Blue whale", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5ff511a7ff04d658268c92c8", "question": "Who was Canada's longest-serving prime minister?", "answer": "William Lyon Mackenzie King was Canada's longest serving prime minister at 21 years, 154 days, non-consecutively.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339909", "question": "What baseball movie features a character nicknamed Nuke LaLoosh?", "answer": "Bull Durham", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b858", "question": "What was the first sport to be televised in the US?", "answer": "Baseball", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5e8a67ea9a45431f553a9cd3", "question": "What is the name of Charles Dickens' thirteenth novel?", "answer": "Great Expectations", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe9396d6bd93ce3a4e5f68d", "question": "What temperature is absolute zero?", "answer": "-273.15\u00b0C or -459.67\u00b0F", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339266", "question": "What is baby Superman called on the planet Krypton?", "answer": "Kal-El", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e96", "question": "What Tennessee Williams title character is married to Brick Pollitt?", "answer": "Maggie the Cat", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5be57efc5415ba52ed6f0aa8", "question": "Viticulture is the growing and harvesting of what plants?", "answer": "Grapes", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ae2a", "question": "In which decade was the Hindenburg disaster?", "answer": "1930s", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b469", "question": "What English city was once known to the Romans as Venta Belgarum?", "answer": "Winchester", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339393", "question": "In how many Superman movies did Gene Hackman appear as Lex Luthor?", "answer": "Three", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c888", "question": "What scoop out cirques, coombs, and corries?", "answer": "Glaciers", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5c3e9ae8ebfabb9c85d8a980", "question": "The \"Althing\" is the national parliament of which country?", "answer": "Iceland", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f031133889c", "question": "Who said: \"I've had such a curious dream\"?", "answer": "Alice", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a43c", "question": "The Orient Express train originally ran from Paris to where?", "answer": "Istanbul", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133998f", "question": "What year was the movie \"Star Trek: The Motion Picture\" released?", "answer": "1979", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5b358c2c5db0d66a186cb55b", "question": "Popular in the Balkans, what type of beverage is the \"Rakia\"?", "answer": "Fruit brandy", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59e6b2fffb6c85e9e634ff41", "question": "Despite being released at the end of 1998, who had a  #1 hit in 1999 with the song \"Fly Away\"?", "answer": "Lenny Kravitz", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca29", "question": "Where on the human body is the ulnar loop?", "answer": "Finger", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a841", "question": "The ancient city of Troy was located in what is now what country?", "answer": "Turkey", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339797", "question": "What is the favorite food of the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles?", "answer": "Pizza", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388e0", "question": "Who wrote the first three books of the \"Millennium\" novel series?", "answer": "Stieg Larsson", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ad9e1b6e748bb36357acdf6", "question": "Who is the singer behind the albums \"1989\" and \"Reputation\"?", "answer": "Taylor Swift", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2f6", "question": "What 1966 science fiction film staring Raquel Welch did Richard Fleischer direct?", "answer": "Fantastic Voyage", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5cd40b2e685cf15b733e9888", "question": "What South American country's name comes from the Latin word for silver?", "answer": "Argentina", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5c028d55ea32143fcb1d3b58", "question": "In which state is Walla Walla County located?", "answer": "Washington", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b127", "question": "In what city was the UN charter signed?", "answer": "San Francisco", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133992c", "question": "What former big city mayor was the judge on \"The People\u2019s Court\" from 1997 to 1999?", "answer": "Ed Koch", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b975", "question": "Which Birthsign spans the months of January and February?", "answer": "Aquarius", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133907f", "question": "Who wrote a book about John Harrison, entitled \"Longitude\"?", "answer": "Dava Sobel", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ffcfd279dc5ec6cd98a8321", "question": "Who painted Nu couch\u00e9?", "answer": "Amedeo Modigliani", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113389cd", "question": "What literary character is adopted by Messua and her husband who believe him to be their long-lost sibling?", "answer": "Mowgli", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5be580c25415ba52ed6f0ab8", "question": "Doha is the capital of which country?", "answer": "Qatar", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "58b3724d1c3f17ccc40c8e23", "question": "What English party was politician Arthur Hayday associated with?", "answer": "Labour Party", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b038", "question": "Instead of bombs, what did the British Royal Air Force drop on Germany in early WWII?", "answer": "Propaganda leaflets", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe527021bf59ab7d2e380f8", "question": "Who was named as the athlete with the highest career earnings in 2017?", "answer": "Michael Jordan", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c58d", "question": "By what name is the spinal disease \"amyotrophic lateral sclerosis\" better known?", "answer": "Lou Gehrig's disease", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c918", "question": "Lockjaw is another name for which disease?", "answer": "Tetanus", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5ff0b6cde662d71a5365100e", "question": "The book \"Lord of Light\", was written by whom?", "answer": "Roger Zelazny", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e6c", "question": "Who played the blind character in the movie \"Daredevil\"?", "answer": "Ben Affleck", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c960", "question": "What name is given to a doctor who specializes in skin disorders?", "answer": "Dermatologist", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c68d", "question": "The leaves of the eucalyptus tree are the only food that what animal will eat?", "answer": "The koala", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b37e", "question": "The Mason-Dixon line ran between Maryland and which other American State?", "answer": "Pennsylvania", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c350", "question": "What object is theorized to lie at the center of the Milky Way?", "answer": "A black hole", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9aa", "question": "What mountain is the tallest point in Australia?", "answer": "Kosciusko", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fd81bbdd0de9af39e9d467c", "question": "Who was the first president to have electricity in the White House?", "answer": "Benjamin Harrison", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58c8a77a90aac110e4167087", "question": "What mass market tea brand shares a name with an English brewery?", "answer": "Tetley", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c09c", "question": "What wine barrel contains 126 gallons?", "answer": "Pipe or butt", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bacb", "question": "What is the International Criminal Police Organization better known as?", "answer": "Interpol", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a061", "question": "Who sang \"I Want My MTV\" on the Dire Straits song \"Money For Nothing\"?", "answer": "Sting", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59e804aade59ea584496fea6", "question": "In which sport must the ball have a diameter of at least 42.67 millimetres and weigh no less than 45.93 grams?", "answer": "Golf", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5f9f44bfaf848b908361b871", "question": "What is the largest Caribbean island?", "answer": "Cuba", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a610", "question": "What is the world\u2019s most southerly capital city?", "answer": "Wellington", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339747", "question": "What Survivor contestant voted out her own mother in Blood Vs. Water?", "answer": "Ciera Eastin", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339158", "question": "What popular artist sang the words: \"I'm afraid of Americans\"?", "answer": "David Bowie", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c63b", "question": "Which blood type is a universal? donor", "answer": "O negative", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5e910566d7247dfc0fa00312", "question": "When did scientists Glenn T. Seaborg, Albert Ghiorso, Stanley G. Thompson and Kenneth Street, Jr. discover the element Berkelium?", "answer": "December 1949", "category": "science"}, {"id": "597cd690e347d002c297e4bb", "question": "Collectively, what name is given to the first ten of the amendments to the United States Constitution?", "answer": "The Bill of Rights", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5b7ffbaa3a3a814d89068c68", "question": "What is Freddie Mercury's birth name?", "answer": "Farrokh Bulsara", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c8dc", "question": "The name for this semi-precious stone comes from the Latin for \"sea water\"?", "answer": "Aquamarine", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd23", "question": "At what university was Gatorade invented, in 1965?", "answer": "The University of Florida", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a43e", "question": "Greenland is part of which kingdom?", "answer": "Kingdom of Denmark", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bed3", "question": "What game did Charles Darrow based upon the \"The Landlord's Game\"?", "answer": "Monopoly", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a8e9", "question": "What island in Manila Bay was the site of a famous 1942 siege?", "answer": "Corregidor", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe6559aae7e414034b5aeb5", "question": "Which Norse god\u2019s image is Santa Claus partially based on?", "answer": "Odin", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113393eb", "question": "In an episode of \"South Park\", a man in a panda suit was used to teach the public about what?", "answer": "Sexual harassment", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe8a94b01dd7bf43be5e74c", "question": "What is the slogan of Apple Inc.?", "answer": "Think different", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe8b3f901dd7bf43be5e7b8", "question": "How did jaywalking get its name?", "answer": "\"Jay\" was a term for a naive person", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c3b0", "question": "What name is given to the study of volcanoes?", "answer": "Volcanology", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ae6", "question": "What real-life woman, the subject of a 2000 film, won the Miss Pacific Coast beauty pageant in 1981?", "answer": "Erin Brockovich", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59a1a39b12f2a7826b9b8728", "question": "In science and technology, what does the abbreviation \"AI\" stand for?", "answer": "Artificial Intelligence", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fea3f6fff048f679a45ab5e", "question": "Who was the Clark University physicist responsible for \"A Method of Reaching Extreme Altitudes\"?", "answer": "Robert Goddard", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339218", "question": "What is the theme song of the TV show \"Friends\" called?", "answer": "I'll Be There for You by The Rembrandts", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "590721e13745b36be73039fb", "question": "Which Disney character is named after Ebenezer from Charles Dickens\u2019 novel \"A Christmas Carol\"?", "answer": "Scrooge McDuck", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff516f0ff04d658268c92f7", "question": "Egyptian workers were often paid with a ration of what?", "answer": "Beer (It was so beloved in Ancient Egypt that it was an accepted form of currency.)", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113394a2", "question": "What was Michael Flaherty's job on the TV show \"Spin City\"?", "answer": "Deputy mayor", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6007805bbd51d85e222ab644", "question": "What group rebelled against the limitations of Impressionism?", "answer": "The\u00a0Post-Impressionists\u00a0rebelled against the Impressionists' naturalistic depiction of light and color.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca5b", "question": "What is a sternocleidomastoid?", "answer": "A muscle", "category": "science"}, {"id": "60121ab563c99d48cd169b06", "question": "What were clocks missing before 1577?", "answer": "Minute hands", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e30", "question": "In the Harry Potter books, the entrance to Gryffindor Tower is hidden behind a painting of whom?", "answer": "The Fat Lady", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a56b", "question": "In 1620, the Pilgrims established the Plymouth colony in which present-day US state?", "answer": "Massachusetts", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0ac", "question": "What former NFL quarterback was Bob Dole's running mate in the 1996 presidential election?", "answer": "Jack Kemp", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c566", "question": "How many ounces are there in a pound?", "answer": "16", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5ab99adb21a8909e5c332d25", "question": "What is the Kelvin scale used to measure?", "answer": "Temperature", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c93d", "question": "What bird is the smallest living bird?", "answer": "Bee Hummingbird", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b934", "question": "What color is the 3 ball in pool?", "answer": "Red", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ba7", "question": "What museum, designed by Frank Lloyd Wright, was opened in 1959?", "answer": "Guggenheim Museum", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5f95b00855722f97b22684da", "question": "In the \"Harry Potter\" universe, who dies during the third Tri-wizard Tournament?", "answer": "Cedric Diggory", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6f2", "question": "What device was Alexander Graham Bell working, which led him to the invention of the telephone?", "answer": "Hearing aid", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b4c5", "question": "What year marked the appearance of Doc Savage?", "answer": "1933", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59ca3c6344f0f6af5b066630", "question": "Nuclear membrane, cytoplasm, and nucleus are parts of a what?", "answer": "Cell", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fef96566ce05a3942286e9c", "question": "The novel \"Flowers for Algernon\" became which major motion picture?", "answer": "\"Charly\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa1a", "question": "What's the opposite of the Orient?", "answer": "The Occident", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fec8d25ec223966ae8f884f", "question": "Who said this in the movie \"The Shawshank Redemption\"? \"Hope is a dangerous thing. Hope can drive a man insane.\"", "answer": "Red", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a375", "question": "What is the capital of Ukraine?", "answer": "Kiev", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a094", "question": "What song by Don McLean talks about the day Buddy Holly died?", "answer": "American Pie", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ccf7c47b37b32637bdc44c8", "question": "What is the smallest country by area and population?", "answer": "Vatican City", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe4b64a06d333868d34d6f0", "question": "Who first flew an airplane nonstop across the Atlantic?", "answer": "John Alcock and Arthur Brown", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf32", "question": "In Norway what is a Brisling?", "answer": "A Sprat", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113389c4", "question": "What is Mr. Sowerberry's job in Oliver Twist?", "answer": "Undertaker", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fffa94a73838c5c8a417f43", "question": "What can\u2019t a cheetah do that a tiger and a puma can do?", "answer": "Retract its claws", "category": "science"}, {"id": "59049aaecf93664eb1048699", "question": "Who was Joe\u2019s co-creator for the character of Superman?", "answer": "Jerry Siegel", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339368", "question": "In the 1960 movie \"Psycho\", what actor plays the private detective?", "answer": "Martin Balsam", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "594d074f1a1c922dd1ac64b7", "question": "Who was both the 22nd and the 24th president of the United States?", "answer": "Grover Cleveland", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fef91ec6ce05a3942286e7d", "question": "Ray Bradbury's novel \"Fahrenheit 451\" was serialized in which magazine?", "answer": "\"Playboy\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff51ac9ff04d658268c9309", "question": "Which goddess helped guide Odysseus back home?", "answer": "Athena helped guide Odysseus back to Ithaca", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113395fe", "question": "In the 1990 movie \"Pretty Woman\", Julia Roberts is payed to stay for how long with Richard Gere?", "answer": "One week", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f86", "question": "What is the fourth book in the Harry Potter series?", "answer": "The Goblet Of Fire", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396ba", "question": "Which Seinfeld character takes his shirt off when he visits the toilet?", "answer": "George Costanza", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe12f17e39efa6330e0fed6", "question": "Where is Great Sand Dunes National Park?", "answer": "Colorado", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b30", "question": "In \"Dumb & Dumber\", to give back a misplaced briefcase, Harry and Lloyd travel to what US city?", "answer": "Aspen", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113399f2", "question": "Who is the lead guitarist in the band \"The Who\"?", "answer": "Pete Townsend", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339146", "question": "Who created the character Pinocchio?", "answer": "Carlo Collodi", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "601b4c8749076251badbead6", "question": "What was the first country to put a woman in space?", "answer": "The Soviet Union -- In 1963, cosmonaut Valentina Tereshkova\u00a0orbited the Earth 48 times in a space capsule named Vostok 6.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339573", "question": "What musical artist sang, It's the Most Wonderful Time of the Year?", "answer": "Andy Williams", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c19c", "question": "What nationality is tennis player Martina Hingis?", "answer": "Swiss", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bdbc", "question": "What is traditionally the main fruit ingredient in tepenade?", "answer": "Olives", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339541", "question": "On what TV show would you find Powdered Toast Man?", "answer": "The Ren & Stimpy Show", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133905e", "question": "What year did poet Sylvia Plath end her life?", "answer": "1963", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fea48c0ff048f679a45abb3", "question": "Which electronic component can be classified as NPN or PNP?", "answer": "Transistor", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5ff0b3ade662d71a53650fe1", "question": "What unique quirk did Fr\u00e9d\u00e9ric Chopin have?", "answer": "He preferred to play in the dark.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "590722e33745b36be7303a03", "question": "What popular Christmas song did Eartha Kitt record in 1953?", "answer": "Santa Baby", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a571", "question": "Which US state is home to North Cascades National Park?", "answer": "Washington", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339dfa", "question": "What Kansas song does Keanu Reeves use to wow Socrates in \"Bill & Ted's Excellent Adventure\"?", "answer": "Dust in the Wind", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391ac", "question": "What is Homer Simpson's middle initial?", "answer": "J", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b735", "question": "What brand of gasoline introduced an additive called \"Platformate\" in 1968?", "answer": "Shell", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391a2", "question": "Who is known as Eminem?", "answer": "Marshall Mathers", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5bbd4c1c00d154d7af00b8cf", "question": "Who recorded the 1990's song \"Baby Got Back\"?", "answer": "Sir Mix-a-Lot", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aea5", "question": "What famous World War II general went into battle wearing two ivory-handled revolvers on his hips?", "answer": "General George Patton", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b252", "question": "What Ukrainian city hosted the last World War II summit of the \"Big Three\"?", "answer": "Yalta", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fede5cf6ce05a3942286df1", "question": "Which of Santa's reindeer is female?", "answer": "Vixen", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5904a4f5cf93664eb10486c7", "question": "What are the nicknames of the twin sisters who work as enforcers for Darcy Parker, in the \"Strangers in Paradise\" comic series?", "answer": "Tambi and Bambi", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d23", "question": "What sport is the focus of the movie \"National Velvet\"?", "answer": "Horse racing", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5f9f48b3af848b908361b879", "question": "How many people made up the US Electoral College in 2020?", "answer": "538", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59636c72967692ea851899ac", "question": "What popular destination helped popularize hot dogs in the US in the 19th century?", "answer": "Coney Island", "category": "history"}, {"id": "60121c6763c99d48cd169b17", "question": "Who was the designer of the Statue of Liberty?", "answer": "French sculptor Fr\u00e9d\u00e9ric Auguste Bartholdi", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133918c", "question": "Which witch is flattened by a house in \"The Wizard of Oz\"?", "answer": "The Wicked Witch of the East", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ec0", "question": "What country's civil war is the setting for the film \"Blood Diamond\"?", "answer": "Sierra Leone's", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133abdf", "question": "Saipan is the capital of which country?", "answer": "Northern Mariana Islands", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5909caddbb53d1af658864d3", "question": "What ABC Original Movie, starring Jenny McCarthy, air on December 10, 2006?", "answer": "Santa Baby", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be44", "question": "What is the only fruit to be ever banned from airplanes?", "answer": "Durian", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab61", "question": "What city is associated with Alcatraz?", "answer": "San Francisco", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59067f74ff9c0647b50a8084", "question": "On what date did the 2016 Dyn Cyberattack take place, rendering some of the largest Internet services unusable for several hours?", "answer": "October 21, 2016", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe6ab2120565ad31a57c824", "question": "Who said, \"He who wishes to serve his country must have not only the power to think, but the will to act\"?", "answer": "Plato", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339331", "question": "What western drama series told the story of Pat Garrett and Billy the Kid?", "answer": "The Tall Man", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bdc8", "question": "What brand is known as PFK in French-speaking Quebec?", "answer": "KFC", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f2a", "question": "Who wrote \"The Pisan Cantos\" while in prison?", "answer": "Ezra Pound", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fefbf3e6ce05a3942286efc", "question": "Who directed the film \"Top Gun\"?", "answer": "Tony Scott", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5bbc950f60f0007efaba0e60", "question": "In Telltale's Season 1 of the \"The Walking Dead\" game series, what is the name of the main character?", "answer": "Lee", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133971c", "question": "In \"The Addams Family\", what does Morticia do that always excites Gomez?", "answer": "Speaks French", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff0b080e662d71a53650fc9", "question": "Paris\u2019s Centre Pompidou has what architectural quirk?", "answer": "It is \"inside-out\"", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338fc3", "question": "What's the opposite of \"synonym\"?", "answer": "Antonym", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe0de1dfcbed638185eaa12", "question": "Which city has the biggest helicopter fleet in the world?", "answer": "Sao Paulo", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133911c", "question": "Who wrote the 1910 novel \"Howards End\"?", "answer": "E. M. Forster", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a8ab", "question": "In what city would you find Battery Park?", "answer": "New York City", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c572", "question": "What are the four chambers of the heart?", "answer": "Left ventricle, Right ventricle, Left atrium, Right atrium", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113394e5", "question": "Who played the role of Sally McMillan in the TV show \"McMillan & Wife\"?", "answer": "Susan Saint James", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133adda", "question": "In which war was napalm first used?", "answer": "World War II", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fecca43ec223966ae8f8898", "question": "Paul D. Hubbard is the quarterback who is credited with inventing the modern huddle. What affliction did he suffer from?", "answer": "He was deaf and created the huddle so that he can hear teammates better and hide plays from the defending squad.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "600cc2406de0eb824d4052e5", "question": "Norman Rockwell is the official artist of which state?", "answer": "Massachusetts -- He spent 25 years living in the Berkshires of Massachusetts.", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338bb4", "question": "Which famous number was dreaded by people in Orwell\u2019s 1984?", "answer": "101", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fede5c16ce05a3942286df0", "question": "What is the only product Elvis Presley ever did a live TV commercial for?", "answer": "Southern Maid Donuts", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58c89d23011619dd6d415483", "question": "What disappeared from the town of South Park, forcing Randy to relocate his family to a refugee camp in California?", "answer": "The Internet", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fdc1364469bb8041d07a07e", "question": "Which type of pie is traditional at British Christmas feasts?", "answer": "Mince", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c31f", "question": "What is the most common element in air?", "answer": "Nitrogen", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133abf0", "question": "Which seas border Ukraine to the south?", "answer": "Black Sea and Sea of Azov", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f77", "question": "What was Gladys Knight's backing band?", "answer": "The Pips", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fecc83eec223966ae8f8890", "question": "After Andy gets assaulted and beaten, who exacts revenge on the one who perpetrated it in the movie \"The Shawshank Redemption\"?", "answer": "Captain Bryon Hadley cripples Bogs, the leader of the group that assaults Andy.", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58ec22648dc25ca9e12ef626", "question": "Phallophobia is a fear of what?", "answer": "Penis", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339993", "question": "What are the names of Rachael's two sisters on the TV show \"Friends\"?", "answer": "Amy and Jill", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58d11a084fea7fe947a22293", "question": "What is the fear of politicians known as?", "answer": "Politicophobia", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b3bd", "question": "In which country did the Boxer Rebellion take place?", "answer": "China", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5a25efc56682715b82711cd8", "question": "Which Canadian province was responsible for producing the weekly newpaper publication \"Photo Journal\" until 1981?", "answer": "Quebec", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac34", "question": "What is the first word of the text of the US Constitution?", "answer": "We", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c3eb", "question": "What name did Neil Armstrong give to the spot where man first touched down on the Moon?", "answer": "Tranquility Base", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339387", "question": "Who was the Castle Rock DJ in the movie \"Stand By Me\"?", "answer": "Bob Cormier", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c801", "question": "What invisible \"color\" can bees see on flower petals?", "answer": "Ultraviolet, or Bee purple", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c4ca", "question": "What is a young bee fed to develop into a queen?", "answer": "Royal jelly", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ad97", "question": "Who succeeded Spiro Agnew as vice president of the United States?", "answer": "Gerald Ford", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6d4", "question": "What is the atomic number of iodine?", "answer": "53", "category": "science"}, {"id": "59067a74ff9c0647b50a805a", "question": "In 2016, which vessel became the first solar-powered aircraft to circumnavigate the Earth?", "answer": "Solar Impulse 2", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe4df1c06d333868d34d71e", "question": "What is the name of the eon we are living in?", "answer": "Phanerozoic Eon", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391cd", "question": "Who directed the movie \"Alien\"?", "answer": "Ridley Scott", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6012184863c99d48cd169aef", "question": "In regards to data storage, what does the acronym SSD stand for?", "answer": "Solid State Drive", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388b5", "question": "How many strings does the common Bass guitar have?", "answer": "4", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2c4", "question": "Who played the role of Jenna Maroney on the TV show \"30 Rock\"?", "answer": "Jane Krakowski", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391ab", "question": "Who does Emma Watson play in the Harry Potter films?", "answer": "Hermione", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "597cdbd5e347d002c297e4e2", "question": "What meteorological significance is traditionally attached to cows lying down?", "answer": "Rain", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a87b", "question": "In what city would you find the most famous street named \"Nathan Road\"?", "answer": "Hong Kong", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b19c", "question": "What dog breed was the official 1972 Summer Olympics mascot?", "answer": "Dachshund", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fea345bff048f679a45aaf7", "question": "What is the name of the biggest part of the human brain?", "answer": "The cerebrum", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bdf9", "question": "What do James Arness, Michael Crichton, John Kenneth Galbraith, Krist Novoselic and Peter the Great have in common?", "answer": "They are very tall", "category": "general"}, {"id": "6002424c4be4723ccac22183", "question": "In Chaucer\u2019s \"The Canterbury Tales\", the pilgrims are travelling to visit the shrine of which saint?", "answer": "Saint Thomas Becket", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c4d4", "question": "The fruit of the rose plant shares its name with what part of the body?", "answer": "The hips", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113394b7", "question": "Who played the role of Ricky Stratton on the TV show \"Silver Spoons\"?", "answer": "Ricky Schroeder", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b1b9", "question": "What country was called the Gold Coast prior to its 1957 independence?", "answer": "Ghana", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a26c", "question": "What year did Billy Joel release the song \"We Didn't Start the Fire\"?", "answer": "1989", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fdfff3a1cf6db9ac4808d0c", "question": "What is the largest city in the contiguous United States in terms of area?", "answer": "Jacksonville, Florida", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca47", "question": "What is the more common name for grape sugar?", "answer": "Glucose", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe8b5be01dd7bf43be5e7d4", "question": "What snack was invented by monks?", "answer": "Pretzels", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bdd1", "question": "Architect Walter Gropius founded what famous German art school in Weimar in 1919?", "answer": "The Bauhaus", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59a1a3de12f2a7826b9b872a", "question": "Forty six represents the atonomic number of which element?", "answer": "Palladium", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c373", "question": "What disease takes its name from medieval Italian words for \"bad air\"?", "answer": "Malaria", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a840", "question": "The national currency of Panama is named for what Pacific explorer?", "answer": "Balboa", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a88a", "question": "What historic plaza is named for the first publisher of the \"Dallas Morning News\"?", "answer": "Dealey Plaza", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391a9", "question": "Who voices the character of scientist and inventor Professor John I.Q. Nerdelbaum Frink Jr. on \"The Simpsons\"?", "answer": "Hank Azaria", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ffa43a1c73aa70ea0b70b18", "question": "Which African city is famous for its native penguin population?", "answer": "Cape Town, South Africa", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "601debe96b1208747aa7e9d7", "question": "Which famous entrepreneur is credited with inventing the weekend?", "answer": "Henry Ford", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c268", "question": "What is the common name for hydrogen hydroxide?", "answer": "Water", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5febbbbb7e83c707845b214a", "question": "What special title does Anthony Hopkins possess in real life?", "answer": "Sir (Sir Anthony Hopkins was knighted by Queen Elizabeth in 1993, two years after the release of \"the Silence of the Lambs\".)", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "594a61ca2ebb971c1417fb8a", "question": "By what name is \"One Thousand and One Nights\" better known as in the English language?", "answer": "Arabian Nights", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe93a576bd93ce3a4e5f695", "question": "Which extinction event was caused by human activity?", "answer": "Holocene extinction", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a0e9", "question": "In which California city does the 1982 film \"Poltergeist\" take place?", "answer": "Cuesta Verde", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5febaeee7e83c707845b20f9", "question": "What gives eyes their color?", "answer": "Melanin", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fede5216ce05a3942286de7", "question": "What is television chef Rachael Ray's signature phrase?", "answer": "Yum-O", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0ab", "question": "George H.W. Bush served in which branch of the US military?", "answer": "Navy", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59524530736d4be723796b6c", "question": "What French impressionist painter died in 1926", "answer": "Claude Monet", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59636abd967692ea8518999f", "question": "Which two cross-border neighbouring cities jointly celebrate July 1 and July 4 holidays with the International Freedom Festival?", "answer": "Windsor and Detroit", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ff51215ff04d658268c92cd", "question": "Who was the first American casualty in the American Revolutionary War?", "answer": "Crispus Attucks\u00a0was the first person killed in the Boston massacre and is widely considered to be the first American casualty.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b1a", "question": "What was the nickname of character Freddie Stubbs on the 1970's sitcom \"What's Happening!!\"?", "answer": "Rerun", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58f16aa7f7c52aae91cc07df", "question": "In which city is the \"Wailing Wall\"?", "answer": "Jerusalem", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c2c6", "question": "Where does vanilla come from?", "answer": "Orchids", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe6aa5720565ad31a57c816", "question": "The tip of the Washington Monument is made of what?", "answer": "Aluminum", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b88", "question": "What city's opera house does \"The Phantom of the Opera\" prowl?", "answer": "Paris'", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe8b46801dd7bf43be5e7bf", "question": "What Marvel superhero was created to sell orange juice?", "answer": "Captain Citrus", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a291", "question": "Who became Yusuf Islam in 1977?", "answer": "Cat Stevens", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a673", "question": "Which two US states are separated by the Delaware Bay?", "answer": "Delaware and New Jersey", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "601600e0fe83fe1f2a824c59", "question": "What was the name of the first at-home film camera?", "answer": "Kodak #1", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a551", "question": "The San Andreas Fault is located in which state?", "answer": "California", "category": "geography"}]